

Contact:

Mobile

+212669946914

Email:

aminemorchid0895@gmail.com

Linkedin:

@amine-morchid-1809a7187

Github:

https://github.com/mmorchid08

Address:

khouribga, maroc

Personal skills:

Problem Solving

Team work

Interests:

cars

karting

Personal Profile

I am a Mobile Developer and problem solver with industry experience building mobile applications.

Projects & Experiences

 Forecast Weather Mobile Application / Swift

This project is meant to create a mobile application that provides users with

information about the weather per each city using Weather API

42sh / C Language

This project is meant to create a shell capable of reading and evaluating any user command

• Roger-Skyline

Roger-Skyline a 42 project meant to learn about the basics of networking and security, the goal is to protect a server from attacks.

• FdF/ C Programming

3D wireframe viewer.

Career Summary

Internship as Mobile developer

Joodek Start-Up june 2021 till now

IT Technical Support Voluntary

Minister of Education April 2020 to June 2020

 support for students, teachers and parents throughout the distance education operation

Mobile Phone Hardware and Software Repair Technician

PLATINIUM COMPUTERS S.A.R.L Aug. 2014 to Jan 2019

- Interact with customers and identify issues.
- Fix and rectify the software faults in Smartphone.
- Perform hardware parts replacements.

Professional Skills

Coding Languages:

C, Dart, Shell, Swift, HTML/CSS.

Frameworks/Systems:

Flutter, Unix/Linux, git

Educational Training

Feb 2019 - Now in khouribga

1337 Coding Shcool

Sep 2015 - Jun 2017 / Specialized Technician Degree

electromechanical automatic system - specialized institute of applied technology - Khouribga (Morocco)

Sep 2014 - Jun 2015 / 1st year

Physics option - Faculty Of Khouribga (Morocco)

Sep 2014 - Jun 2015 / 1st year

BenSouda School Baccalaureate in SVI

Languages

Arabic

Maternal language

English

Intermediate level

French

Intermediate level